iceonline.in 2019-08-09

# Privacy Policy

Very Warm welcome to Institutes For Competitive Exams group’s website www.iceonline.in. This site is owned & operated by Institutes For Competitive Exams one of the companies of Institutes For Competitive Exams Group & is protected by trademark laws & copyright. Your visit to our website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.

For Online order process we may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner, including personal information. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number; your likeness; and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information. Your personal information is collected for our administrative and statistical purposes. We also, upon your consent, may use this information for notifying you concerning our new offers and promotions, organizing delivery and changes in our services.

We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you. Examples of information that we may receive include: updated delivery and address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.

After your visit of our website, your browser may receive a small file from us, called cookie. The file will be stored on your hard drive. The purpose of this file is to identify you when you access our website. This is important for us, because we can spot each new user and deliver more individualized service. Your browser will provide information whether you already have cookies from us and if not, we will send you new ones. Any users who don’t want benefit of cookies may remove cookies.

We reserve the right to send you e-mail relating to your account status. This may includes order confirmations, renewal/expiration notices of credit card problems, other transactional e-mails and notifications about major changes to our site.

We Institutes For Competitive Exams reserve the right to change any terms & conditions in our policy without prior notice. All the changes in our privacy policy will be posted here. Please check this section from time to time.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

Head Office

"Institutes For Competitive Exams" 2nd Floor Shree Satguru Shopping Centre Kalawad Road Near Akshar Mandir, Opp Tirupati Petrol pump, India, Gujarat, Rajkot 360007

(M) +91 9375701110 +91 9328001110
